fantasyguru.com 2019-12-29

# Privacy Policy - Fantasy Guru

**GURU FANTASY REPORTS, INC. PRIVACY POLICY**

_Last updated: 12/11/19_

Guru Fantasy Reports, Inc. (“ **Guru Fantasy Reports** ,” “ **we** ,” “ **us** ,” or “ **our** ”) owns and operates its fantasy sports websites located at FantasyGuru.com, EliteFantasy.com, and EliteSportsBetting.com and related applications, content, products, tools, features, subscriptions, and services (collectively, the “ **Services** ”). **PLEASE READ OUR TERMS OF SERVICE FOR DETAILED INFORMATION ABOUT OUR SERVICES AND YOUR LEGAL OBLIGATIONS.**  

This Privacy Policy (the “ **Policy** ”) is intended to provide information on how we collect, process, and share your personal data. Personal data – or personal information – is any information that relates to you – an identified or identifiable natural person.   When we use the terms “ **you** ” or “ **your** ” in this Policy, we are referring to individuals who access or use our Services in any way.

**Our Services are available only to residents of the United States and Canada who are 18 years of age or older.   If you are located outside the US or Canada, you are prohibited from registering for an account or accessing the Services in any way.**

After reading this Policy, if you have additional questions or would like further information, please contact us at [support@fantasyguru.com](mailto:support@fantasyguru.com).

**PERSONAL DATA WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT** ****

As further explained below, we collect and process your personal data only for lawful reasons, such as our legitimate business interests, your consent, or to fulfill our legal or contractual obligations.  

Information You Provide to Us  
When you use our Services, we may ask you to provide certain personal data. Depending on the activity you are attempting to complete, this may include any of the following:

  * Name
  * Username
  * Email address
  * Address, city, state/province, country, zip
  * Credit card or other payment information
  * Your company
  * Profile picture
  * Any other personal information you provide to us at your option, including in articles, comments, chat rooms, or other online communication forums

We use the data you provide to set up your account, provide the Services, and communicate with you.  We also may use your contact information to periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers, or other information which we think you may find interesting using the information that you have provided.  You are always able to opt-out of these marketing communications by contacting us at [support@fantasyguru.com](mailto:support@fantasyguru.com) or clicking the “unsubscribe” link in the communication.

Usage Information

We may collect, use, and/or store certain standard web measurements and tracking technologies, such as “cookies,” web server logs, or other statistics programs to collect usage information, track and record how you use our Services, and coordinate services with our partners and affiliates.  Guru Fantasy Reports and its analytics partners use cookies and similar technologies to provide, market, and improve the Services, including to keep track of your preferences and profile information, customize services and content, measure promotional effectiveness, and to secure your accounts.  You have options to control or limit how we or our partners use cookies and similar technologies.  For more information, please see [www.allaboutcookies.org/cookies](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/cookies).

Third Party Advertising

We may use third-party advertising companies and/or media partners to serve ads on our Services and/or on other websites on which we advertise. Please note that these companies may use usage information about your visit to our Services, or other sites in accordance with the policies on those sites, in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. We may use usage information and compile aggregate data about it in order to improve our Services, target the advertising, and assess the general effectiveness of such advertising.

Third parties may also place cookies or other tracking technologies to collect information about your use of the Services. We also allow other third parties (e.g., ad networks and ad servers) to serve tailored ads to you on the Services, and to access their own cookies or other tracking technologies device you use to access the Services.  If you wish to opt out of interest-based advertising, click [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). Please note, you will continue to receive generic ads.

**HOW WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION**

When we share your information with third parties, we do so lawfully and only to provide the Services or for other legitimate business or legal purposes as described below:

  * We may share your information with our service providers, partners, sponsors, or affiliates in order to provide the Services, communicate with you, and store your data.
  * We may disclose your information in response to any subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process we receive, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or to defend against legal claims.
  * We may share your information with third-party analytics or advertising partners.
  * We may disclose your information when we believe it appropriate in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding possible illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Terms of Service for the Services you accessed, and/or to protect our rights and property.

As we continue to develop our business, we may sell, buy, or partner with other companies or businesses. In such event, we may transfer or assign the information we have collected as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In such transactions, your personal data may be among the transferred assets.

Also, in the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors’ rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal data is treated, transferred, or used and your personal data may be included in the transferred assets.

Credit Card/Payment Information

If you are purchasing our Services, you may be asked to provide credit card or other payment information. In such event, it is our policy to redirect you to a payment processing portal hosted by a third-party payment processor.  We do not collect, access, store, or process any credit card or payment information. Please see our payment processor’s privacy policy regarding the use, storage, and protection of your credit card information before submitting any credit card information.

**ONLINE CHAT ROOMS,FORUMS, ARTICLES, AND COMMENTS**

We make chat rooms, articles, and similar content areas available for public comments and discussions with other users. Your username and profile picture will be visible to other users and potentially the public when you use our chat rooms and content areas.  We cannot control the information that is shared by other users.

Please remember that any information you voluntarily post in our chat rooms, content areas, comments, or any public area of the internet may be viewable by other members or the public at large . Please exercise caution when deciding to post your views and personal data via our Services.

You will not be able to remove your content after you have posted it.  Our administrators may delete or modify your posts in their sole discretion.  If you have an issue with any posts, you may contact [support@fantasyguru.com](mailto:support@fantasyguru.com).

**HOW WE PROTECT YOUR DATA**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. We have implemented commercially reasonable technical measures to protect against the risks of unauthorized access to, erroneous disclosure of, and unlawful interception of personal data submitted via our Services or otherwise collected or possessed by us. 

While we take reasonable precautions against possible security breaches, no website or internet transmission is completely secure and we cannot guarantee that unauthorized access, hacking, data loss or other breach will never occur. In the event that any information under our control is compromised as a result of a breach of security, we will take reasonable steps to investigate the situation and where appropriate, notify those individuals whose information may have been compromised and take other steps, in accordance with any applicable laws and regulations.

**INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS** ****

We currently do not intentionally accept users from outside the United States or Canada, and we will take reasonable steps to delete any data we receive from outside those countries. If you provide us data from outside the United States, it will necessarily be transferred to the United States for processing and storage, and by using the Services, you consent to such transfer.  

**THIRD PARTY LINKS**

Our Services may contain links to other websites, which may have privacy policies that differ from our own. We are also not responsible for any information or content contained on such sites. Your browsing, use, and interaction on any other websites, including websites which have a link to our Services, are subject to that third-party website’s own rules and policies. Please review the privacy policy posted on any website that you may access through, or which links to, our Services.

**CHILDREN** ****

Our Services are not intended for children under 18 years of age.  Do not sign up with our Services or send us any information if you are under 18 years of age.  If you believe we have collected any personal information from a child younger than 13 years of age, please notify us immediately at [support@fantasyguru.com](mailto:support@fantasyguru.com).

**ACCESS, MODIFY, AND DELETE YOUR DATA** ****

Subject to the limitations discussed above regarding chat rooms, articles, and other content areas, you may have the right to request access to your data or to modify or delete your data.  Please make such requests at [support@fantasyguru.com](mailto:support@fantasyguru.com).

**CONTACT US**

If you have any questions regarding this information or our privacy practices, or if you wish to make a complaint, email us at [support@fantasyguru.com](mailto:support@fantasyguru.com), or write to us at:

Guru Fantasy Reports, Inc.  
401 Park Avenue South  
10th Floor  
New York, NY 10016    
Thank you for visiting our site!
